(Girl:)- Howard?
- Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Howard is employing
a schoolyard paradigm...
(Sheldon:)...in which you are
for all intents and purposes deceased.
(Sheldon:)He intends to act on this
by not speaking to you...
(Sheldon:)...feigning an inability to hear you
when you speak...
(Sheldon:)...and otherwise refusing to acknowledge
your existence.
That's ridiculous.
Why are you cooperating with him?
(Sheldon:)I don't make the rules, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Howard, come on. I didn't plan on this.
(Leonard:)These things just happen.
Usually not to me, but they do happen.
(Howard:)Did someone just feel a cold breeze?
(Sheldon:)I believe this is an extension
of the death metaphor.
(Sheldon:)The cold breeze
is a so-called ectoplasmic issue...
(Sheldon:)...of a disembodied soul passing by.
(Raj:)You know, screw it.
I'm just gonna eat the dumpling.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Oh, hi, Steph.
- Hey.
(Leonard(answering door):)- Come on in.
- Oh, is this a bad time?
(Leonard:)Yeah, but I don't see a better one
on the horizon, so...